( THUNDER RUMBLING )
( PATRICIA SHRIEKING )
( PATRICIA SCREAMING )
Please .
Please don 't hurt me .
It 's wrong ! She 's too young !
The sins of the flesh will ruin her .
Please don 't hurt me ! Please !
( GROWLING )
( CLINKING )
( SCREAMING )
The wicked will be punished .
( EXCLAIMING FEARFULLY )
( GROWLING )
" The mystery heart condition
" that has killed over 30 people in less than four years
" has claimed another victim . "
" Doctors are baffled as to why seemingly fit and healthy people
" are suffering massive heart attacks .
" Many of Fairwater 's residents are claiming that the shadow of Death
" has once again descended on the town . "
What 's this shadow of Death stuff ? I don 't like it .
It 's what they 're saying , Miss Rees-Jones .
There 's a lot of scared people out there .
MAGDA : " For decades , the name of Fairwater has been synonymous with Death
" following the infamous 1964 Bradley-Bartlett murder spree .
" Thirty years later as the death toll steadily rises
" it appears the Grim Reaper has once again returned
" to the quiet streets of Fairwater . "
Oh , no .
Steve , nо .
I asked for a new angle . Now give me something fresh .
I want to see the human face of this tragedy .
Get out there . Talk to the families .
I want to know how this thing has impacted on the local community .
Yes , Miss Rees-Jones .
And Steve , no more references to death as a person .
( INDISTINCT )
Friend of the family ? Really such a shame .
Get out . Go on , get out . Go on .
Go .
Oh , damn .
( TRUCK HORN BLARING ) ( SCREAMING )
Oh , no !
RAY : Oh , my God !
Oh , my God , I don 't believe this . This is not happening .
My lawn , you ruptured my lawn .
Whoa !
Hey . How you doing ?
Just give me a call . I 'll pay for the damages .
You 're damn right you 're gonna pay
'cause I 'm gonna sue your ass .
Now let 's not get litigious , all right ?
Just send me a bill .
" Frank Bannister , Psychic Investigator " ?
That 's right . Well , that 's a good one .
How come you didn 't see the corner coming ? You stupid moron .
This is goddamn bullshit !
Listen , buddy , this is gonna cost you big time .
You 're paying for a new fence , you hear me ?
I want this lawn completely resurfaced .
Or we 're going to talk about a ...
( EXCLAIMING ) Budzo ! My Budzo .
I got your license plate number , you bastard !
This is private property .
Oh ! Mrs. Bradley ? I 'm Dr. Lynskey .
I work at the medical center .
No , you don 't . I know who works there .
I started there three months ago .
Dr. Kamins is my personal physician .
Yes , well , Dr. Kamins is attending a funeral
and I 'm seeing his patients today .
She was cutting the vegetables and the knife slipped .
Well , a couple of stitches and she 'll be fine .
I 'll drive you to the clinic .
That 's impossible .
It 's a deep cut .
Then leave her some antibiotics .
Mother , please .
Patricia never leaves the house .
But it hurts .
To your room , this instant !
Wait , just a minute .
Who did that to you ?
I think you 'd better go now , Dr. Lynskey .
You don 't know who my daughter is , do you ?
Patricia 's not to be trusted .
I beg your pardon ?
I can have her locked up anytime I want to .
They said she was an accessory after the fact .
I know the truth .
It was cold-blooded murder .
( SHOTGUN FIRING )
( WAILING )
FEMALE PRESENTER ON TV : In the space of 27 blood-soaked minutes
12 innocent people gunned down
by hospital orderly John Charles Bartlett .
Patients , medical staff , visitors ,
no one was spared in this madman 's rampage
through Fairwater Sanatorium .
Not even the hospital chapel provided sanctuary
as those in prayer were gunned down on their knees .
FEMALE REPORTER : For heaven sakes !
We 're reporters , for God 's sakes .
We 're supposed to get the news .
FEMALE PRESENTER : A seemingly senseless crime .
Bartlett 's motive remains a mystery to this day .
MALE REPORTER : Johnny Bartlett .
He 's got a demonic look on his face .
Can I talk to you ? Later .
Any comments , Johnny ?
Got me a score of 12 , sir .
That 's one more than Starkweather .
FEMALE PRESENTER : Six years earlier , Charles Starkweather
had murdered 11 people in a Nebraska killing spree .
Guess that makes me public enemy number one !
FEMALE PRESENTER : Fifteen-year-old Patricia Ann Bradley ,
daughter of the hospital administrator
was also implicated in the killings .
She was madly in love with the psychopath , Bartlett .
That 's her .
I was in her house this afternoon .
( PANTING )
Well , that 's just terrific , honey .
We 've been in town for three months
and you 're making friends with the Manson Family .
FEMALE PRESENTER : 2 , 200 volts of electricity
ended the life of Johnny Bartlett , the unrepentant killer .
As they threw the switch he was heard to scream :
" I got me a score of 12 . Beat that . "
( ELECTRICITY CRACKLING )
In what some considered a miscarriage of justice
Patricia Ann Bradley was sentenced to life imprisonment
although it was never proven that she actively participated
in the killings .
Five years ago , Patricia Bradley
was granted a conditional release
by the State Governor .
Today she lives a reclusive life back in the family home ...
Should 've fried her when they fried Bartlett .
She was 15 years old , you know .
She just fell in love with the wrong guy .
It could happen to anyone .
Sweetie , I don 't want you going back up there .
The place gives me the creeps .
I really don 't think that you should ...
Come on , honey .
( GROWLING PLAYFULLY )
I think Tiger 's getting a little lonely .
Guess what I did tonight , honey .
I made reservations at Excalibur 's .
Don 't you remember , sweetheart ?
It 's our anniversary this Tuesday .
I even got our favorite table .
Yeah ? You silly willy ?
What the hell is this doing here ?
I thought I tore this up .
Did he come back to the house ? Who ?
That moron that tore up my fence !
( GASPING ) ( DOORS RATTLING )
( SCREAMING )
Help ! Ray , help .
He 's alive .
Ray !
Ray , get me off !
( PANTING )
( SCREAMING )
You sick thing !
Lucy , I don 't want that con man in my house .
There 's gotta be some kind of rational explanation for all this .
I just don 't want some goddamn spoon bender telling me what to do .
Ray , we have got a poltergeist !
Well , it 's nothing that the police can 't handle .
( PHONE RINGING )
Bannister .
Dr. Lynskey , I 'm on my way .
Ah ! Persistent residue of the departed .
Always a problem this time of year .
Dr. Lynskey ?
Ah , yes . Thank you for coming .
Yeah .
The activity is currently located where ?
Well , I don 't know . It just went quiet about five minutes ago .
Went quiet ?
The dining room table spun in a counterclockwise direction ?
I don 't think that that one happened . No .
The toilet seat lid banged up and down ?
No .
Did the bed levitate ?
Yeah , with me on it .
Spontaneous recurrent psychokinesis . Oh , boy .
This could be the worst case I 've ever seen .
Yeah , this is bad .
Mmm-hmm .
Okay . Well , folks , I can do a clearance
but it 's not gonna be cheap .
Although I do offer a six-month guarantee .
How much ?
$ 249 . 95 .
But there is a 30 % surcharge
for making a house call after midnight .
Then there 's vehicle , gas ,
so I 'd say the whole thing is gonna set you back
somewhere in the neighborhood of $ 450 .
( EXCLAIMS )
( MOUTHING )
Although we could forget about the fence ,
call the whole thing even .
( MOUTHING ) Do it .
Okay . Excuse me , ma 'am . You wanna stand back .
I don 't want you to have to sign a waiver .
Plus a $ 100 for materials . I can 't be out of pocket .
Just do it , for Christ 's sakes , Bannister .
Here we go .
All righty .
Why us ? I mean , why are they in our house ?
All I can tell you is emanations are
normally confined to the cemetery
although they do escape .
It 's usually the young ones .
For God 's sakes , Bannister , come on .
Come on .
( MACHINERY WHIRRING )
( GASPS )
( GUN WHIRRING ) It 's Holy water .
This is bullshit . This is total bullshit .
Come on . Yes !
Okay , these belong to you .
Six ectoplasmic emanations .
Don 't worry . They can 't escape .
Some people like a souvenir . Where would you like me to put them ?
No . I really don 't think we wanna hang onto those .
So , thank you .
Do we , hon ?
I could give a rat 's ass .
Okay .
Don 't worry , they can 't feel a thing .
At least that 's what it says in the book .
You never really know for sure .
All right . Thank you , Bannister .
You can go .
What the hell are you staring at ?
What 's with the number ?
What number ?
( SCOFFS ) Look , if you 're trying to freak me out , it 's not gonna work , okay ?
You know what he 's trying to do ?
He 's trying to get more money out of us is what he 's trying to do .
Here , take your shit and get the hell out of my house .
Come on .
Move .
( GUN WHIRRING ) Ray , just ...
Thank you so much .
There you go . Thanks .
Thank you .
Why do you always have to alienate everybody ?
( GRUNTS )
I think I 'm going to throw up .
Damn .
( GAGGING )
( GRUNTS )
Man , I hate that trunk !
Yeah , I don 't want you guys spreading your ectoplasmic muck
all over my car seats .
Ain 't that a bitch .
The ectoplasm 's the only thing sticky enough to hold the damn car together .
Look , Frank , I 'm sorry about your pus yellow , piece-of-shit Volvo
but we ain 't riding in the damn trunk no more , you understand ?
We would like to cruise with some style , man .
You know , you guys left me high and dry tonight .
I get to the house , nothing 's happening .
I couldn 't believe it .
( EXCLAIMS )
Stuart , in or out ?
( STRUGGLING )
You guys didn 't even bang the toilet seat lid ?
You made me look like an asshole .
We strained our backs lifting that heavy ass bed , Frank .
Yeah . Who was the idiot
who put the number in the guy 's forehead ?
It wasn 't funny .
Start pulling your weight , guys
or you 're going back to the cemetery . ( MOUTHING )
Yeah , well , you can pull this , Frank .
I 'm about to go like Jesse on your ass .
I 'm gonna find me some other black ghosts and then organize a march .
The African American Apparition Coalition . The AAAC .
And I 'm gonna tell you something , Frank !
There ain 't nothing worse than a bunch of pissed off brothers that 's already dead !
Will someone help me , please ?
Stu , man , you gotta loosen up , man . I 'm serious .
Come on . Looser , just loosen up , okay ? You lose ? All right .
( GROANS )
You 're so tight you can play " Pick up sticks " with your butt cheeks .
( GRUNTS )
Loosen up . There you go .
Damn !
That fellow takes us totally for granted .
And we 're supposed to be his business partners .
What a joke !
I 'm gonna straighten him out . First thing in the morning .
He 's dealing with a double major here .
Well , no more Mr. nice guy .
I 'm gonna get rough !
FRANK : You talking to me , Stuart ? No .
See , Stuart , that 's your problem . You 're too soft with him .
You gotta just walk up to Frank ,
just look him in the eye and just say ,
Frank , give me what I want or I 'm gonna bust your ass !
Yo , Frank ! How 's it hanging ?
I don 't know , Cyrus . You tell me .
Well , Frank , I 'll tell you .
The women ain 't missing nothing !
Hey , come on . I told you guys ,
get the hell out of my plumbing .
Hey , look , come on , Frank !
Look , we want to call a meeting , man . We gotta ...
Hey , Cyrus . I gotta take a leak .
And I 'm not getting out of the shower .
Goodbye .
Therefore , a happy ghost is a productive ghost .
( FLY BUZZING )
To that end , I 've drawn up a list of suggestions .
Now bear in mind , Frank
that we have given you five years of loyal service .
Flies . That 's what you 've given me , Stuart . Flies .
Why is it that flies stick to you guys like shit to a blanket ?
Ha-ha ! Very funny . You a funny guy , Frank .
You know , all you think about is yourself .
You know , I can complain , too , you know .
I would like some new clothes . You get to dress nicely .
I am still looking like Linc from The Mod Squad .
You died in the 70s . It 's a bummer .
( FLY BUZZING )
I think what Cyrus is attempting to say , Frank ,
is that we don 't feel that the enterprise is evolving
in quite the manner in which we all agree .
Please don 't reach through me when I 'm trying to speak to you .
( CHOKING )
CYRUS : Now , Frank , we gotta talk about cigars .
FRANK : Cigars ? Damn right .
You 've been promising a box for I don 't know how long .
Cyrus , I hate to break this to you but you 're dead , you know .
You can 't smoke .
Well , you can light them up and blow the smoke in my face .
If I light up a cigar , I 'll blow my lunch in your face .
( RUSTLER WHINING )
Everybody , get down ! Goddamn it , Judge !
( SCREAMING )
Put the shooters away .
Whoa !
That was a head shot , Frank . He could have killed me .
You know , if I wanted to get shot at every day
I 'd move my black ass to Los Angeles !
( GASPS )
( BUZZING )
When a man 's jawbone drops off
it 's time to reassess the situation .
I got myself a nice little grave
up there at the cemetery .
It could soon be time to lay my bones .
No , you 're my go-to guy .
Without you , I 'm out of business , Judge .
Frightening ,
that 's a young man 's game , Frank .
I ain 't got no more hauntings left in me .
What are you talking about ? You 're in great shape .
My joints are getting powdery .
The dog 's running away with my face .
Hell , I 'm falling apart .
You 've been falling apart for years .
Don 't go saying nothing to the boys
but my ectoplasm is all dried up .
I 'm sorry to hear that , Judge .
Give it up , Frank .
Death ain 't no way to make a living .
Yeah , well , Judge , I gotta finish this house .
You ain 't never gonna finish this house .
You ain 't never gonna finish nothing !
You 're fooling yourself , Frank !
Too many skeletons in the closet .
( GROWLING )
It 's us , Frank .
What do you think ? Pretty scary , huh ?
Don 't you ever do that again .
Maybe we should try a white sheet next time .
Ain 't gonna be no white sheets , bro .
Oh ? Huh ?
Morning , Zach .
Frank .
Okay . You guys wanna talk , let 's talk .
Let 's talk about this .
This is a letter from my bank .
This says they want $ 15 , 000 from me or they 're gonna sell my house .
Well , cool ! About time we ditched this drafty ass crib
and moved to some place nice with some glass in the windows .
Hey , Cyrus , this is serious shit , okay ?
This is my house . I 'm not losing it !
Stuart .
The chicken , the chicken was not scary , Stuart .
The chicken was stupid .
( SNORTS )
Judge , help me out here , okay ?
Talk to these guys . They look up to you , all right ? Thanks .
I need $ 15 , 000 , guys . I need it quick .
It is time to get seriously scary .
CYRUS : So you checked the place out , right ?
STUART : Right .
How many we got in here ?
Five . They won 't suspect a thing .
Hmm .
Poor suckers . They won 't even know what him ' em . How many exits ?
Two .
( CLEARS THROAT )
All right , man , this is it . We gotta be hard . No mercy .
We 're going in like professionals , like Charles Bronson .
We don 't stop till the screaming starts , you dig ?
I 'm with you .
Let 's go .
Yeah .
Let 's kick some ass .
Here we go . One , two , three ...
Good morning , my darlings . Hello .
The mail 's on the table , Mrs. Waterhouse .
Thank you , Sylvia .
Sylvia , Mother is coming for lunch . Pick up , quick .
Yes , ma 'am .
Big kiss .
All right , kid , quit jumping around and acting like a baby .
This is serious .
Now , we 're gonna scare the living daylights out of your parents .
So , come on , kid , you gonna help us out ?
Are you with us ?
See ? He gets it . The kids always get it .
Let 's go . All right .
( LAUGHS )
Mrs. Waterhouse .
( CHILDREN LAUGHING )
Mrs. Waterhouse !
( EXCLAIMS ) Damn . Here , man . This one did le poo-poo .
Get it away from me .
Man , they 're so little .
Their doo-doo smells like old shoes .
( SCREAMS ) Mrs. Waterhouse !
( SCREAMING )
My babies !
( PHONE RINGING )
Yeah , Frank Bannister .
Uh-huh !
I 'm on my way .
Judge . Need you riding shotgun .
Yes .
Damn it ! Come on , come on . Let 's go . Come on . D for drive .
Look around you , Frank .
Don 't you realize what 's happening ?
Yeah , every other car 's a freaking hearse .
Come on , I can 't even get across town .
This town is in deep trouble .
Yeah . Too many funerals , not enough traffic lights .
It 's death , Frank .
Death is amongst us .
Come on , let 's go . Time is money .
You haven 't heard a goddamn word I 've said .
I thought you had some character , son .
But right now you 're not showing me much .
All right , Judge .
Watch this .
( TIRES SCREECHING )
Look out !
What 's the matter , Judge ? You look a little pale .
Beautiful . Beautiful , Judge .
This is gonna be easy . Why don 't you just rest your bones ?
I 'll be right back .
Ma 'am .
( WHISTLES IN DESPAIR )
Persistent residue of the departed .
It 's always a problem this time of year .
Frank Bannister , I believe you called .
Not a minute too soon . Oh , boy .
CYRUS : Frank , she just ... Shut up .
Frank , it 's no use . She ...
This is bad .
Recurrent spontaneous psychokinesis .
Yeah , this could be the worst case I have ever
seen .
I apologize for calling you , Mr. Bannister .
Please leave .
FRANK : What the hell are you trying to do to me ?
Preying on the bereaved is about as low as you can go .
You 're a parasite , Mr. Bannister , and people should be warned .
Yeah , well , I got a right to offer my services to the public .
In case you hadn 't noticed ,
we are in the midst of a major health crisis .
The last thing the people of Fairwater need is some
two-bit charlatan promising to pass on bogus messages from the other side .
Now , if you will excuse me .
I 'm just trying to make a living .
Living ?
Not a word you 'd know a lot about . Is it , Mr. Bannister ?
Easy . ( GRUNTS )
Asshole .
( HONKING ) ( TIRES SCREECHING )
( EXCLAIMS )
MAN : Whoa ! You all right , buddy ?
Man , you took quite a fall .
Bannister ! Yeah .
Listen , you gotta help .
They 're gonna bury me , man . You gotta help .
Bannister , what is happening to me ?
Well , Ray , you appear to be dead .
Don 't say that . That 's impossible . I 'm in the prime of my life .
I work out every single day . My wife 's a goddamn doctor !
Why didn 't you take the corridor ?
What corridor ?
The corridor of life . The passageway to the other side .
Because I don 't belong on the other side !
Jesus Christ , I 'm only 29 .
( EXCLAIMING )
Hey , hey , hey !
Look , Ray ,
just relax , all right ?
You wanna tell me what happened ?
I was on the rowing machine
and then suddenly I felt this viselike grip
just squeezing my heart and I couldn 't breathe , Frank .
I just couldn 't breathe and ...
I 've got the shakes now . I need some vitamin B.
Yeah , you can 't take vitamins anymore .
You don 't eat , you don 't drink , you don 't go to the bathroom .
All that shit 's over with .
( CRYING )
In about a year 's time you 're gonna get a chance
to go through to the other side again .
To become what 's known as a pure spirit .
But in the meantime ,
you 're what 's known as an earthbound emanation
which is a rotting cloud of bioplasmic particles
dripping ectoplasm from every orifice .
( CRYING )
Relax , Ray .
( BREATHING DEEPLY )
All right , Bannister ,
can you at least give me a ride so I don 't miss my funeral ?
Okay , Ray , listen up .
The cemetery 's not a safe place . All right ? So stay close .
Later , Bannister . I wanna hear what they 're saying about me .
( GRUNTS )
( RAY EXCLAIMING IN FEAR )
Don 't worry about them . They 're not gonna to hurt you .
What in the hell is going on out here ?
Get back in your graves !
Son of a ...
Holy Jesus !
Frank Bannister !
Go ahead . I 'll handle this .
What the hell are you doing in my graveyard ?
You have been told to stay away !
Sound off like you 've got a pair !
Yeah , well , it 's a public place , Hiles .
I do not like you !
You cannot bring your spooks in here without my permission !
Disappear , scumbag !
( GROANS )
I am not one of your shitty little emanations , Bannister .
You cannot push spirits around .
You are scum ! Using spooks to put the frighteners on people !
That makes me physically ill !
We got a lot of lowlifes around here !
And I will provide an armed response at the first sign of trouble !
They must be contained !
( SPIRITS EXCLAIM )
Catch you later , Hiles .
My tour of duty runs another 85 years !
There 's a piece of dirt up here
with your name on it , Bannister !
I 'm waiting for you , you little maggot !
There were times when people have accused Ray of being
less than generous , but I 'm sure , deep down
the man possessed a heart of gold and a generous spirit .
It 's true .
He wouldn 't lie . Not at a time like this .
( SOBBING )
PRIEST : Because God has chosen to call our brother Ray
from this life to Himself
we commit his body to the ground .
Earth to earth , ashes to ashes , dust to dust .
RAY : Jesus , what a waste .
The Lord bless him and keep him .
It 's a goddamn tragedy .
The Lord lift up his countenance upon him and give him peace .
Goodbye , Ray .
Sweetheart , don 't cry .
Oh , shit !
( EXCLAIMING FEARFULLY )
RAY : Frank !
I know you can hear me .
Get me out of this hole , Bannister .
Frank .
Get me out of this hole , please .
Hi , Frank .
Hey , Walt .
Kind of surprised to see you .
Here on business , I guess ?
Not exactly .
Bannister , they 're gonna bury me alive in here .
I understand you and Lynskey had a little run-in
the night before he died .
As a matter of fact , apart from his wife
I believe you were the last person to see him alive .
It sounds like you 're the one who 's here on business , Walt .
No . The FBI is very concerned about these deaths .
They look like heart attacks
but when they slice these people open
their arteries are just clean as a whistle .
But there 's been this tremendous pressure on the heart
like the life has just been crushed right out of it .
You got any theories , Frank ?
Bannister !
Mind if I pay my last respects before they fill him in ?
Oh ! No . I 'm sorry .
Bannister , please .
( INAUDIBLE )
I need to cheer up .
Mr. Bannister ?
Mr. Bannister , did you want to see me ?
Oh , my God , Frank . She can see me .
I thought perhaps you might have a message from Ray .
Tell her . Tell her I 'm here , Frank . Tell her .
I mean , everyone says that you 're a fraud
but I 've seen what you can do .
( SHOUTING ) Frank !
You must think I 'm very stupid .
Excuse me .
Lucy ,
Ray says he loves you very much .
Here you are . Here 's your table .
Hi . Hi . Hi .
( WHISPERS ) Is Ray with us ?
Yeah .
Tell her she looks great .
He says that you look great .
Tell her they 're from me .
Those are from Ray .
It 's our anniversary .
Right . He says it 's your anniversary .
Is Ray beside me ?
He 's over here .
Oh .
Greetings . How are you this evening ?
May I offer you some wine ?
I don 't know . Lucy , do you want some , what , red , white ?
Red , we always have red .
White . I 've never been fond of red .
Lucy !
So you used to be an architect ?
A long time ago . Can it , Bannister .
She doesn 't want to hear your life story .
Wow . So did you build your own house ?
I mean , you must have a dream home .
You could call it a dream home .
I 'm gonna build you a dream home , sweetheart ,
just as soon as I get on my feet .
Yeah .
Tell me , why is it that you can see Ray and I can 't ?
I was in an accident , a car accident
about five years ago .
I don 't know . They say that
sometimes when you have a traumatic experience
that it can alter your perception .
Really , so after that you could just see spirits ?
I mean , what happened ?
How about you talk to Ray ? That 's why I 'm here .
Oh , finally , I 'm in the conversation . Terrific .
Well , actually I do have an important question
that I have to ask Ray .
Well , he can hear you .
Ray , I really need to know where you invested my money ,
the $ 16 , 000 that I had saved .
The attorneys can 't seem to find it anywhere .
Oh , shit . I blew it on a bad investment .
But don 't tell her that . I 'll think of something .
It 's gone , Lucy . It 's gone .
He blew it on a bad investment .
You asshole ! ( SIGHS )
Tell her everything 's gonna be okay .
I 'm gonna look out for her . I 'm gonna move back into the house .
Tell her that . No , that 's not a good idea .
Bannister , this doesn 't concern you .
What 's Ray saying ? What 's he saying ?
He left . Ray left .
He said he was he was sorry ,
but he wanted to leave you alone ,
let you get on with your life .
I swear to God , Bannister , I 'm gonna kill you .
I can 't believe it , I mean ...
That 's just like Ray to just take the money and run , like ...
Ray and I haven 't been honest with each other
in a long time , Mr. Bannister .
( SIGHS )
It wasn 't what you would call a good marriage .
You bitch !
Lucy , it 's gonna be okay .
Get your hands off my wife !
Goddamn it !
Sorry .
( LAUGHS ) I can move shit , Bannister .
Man , you better watch your back .
I better clean this up . I 'll be right back .
Good food , huh ?
Yeah , it 's great .
( PANTING )
( GROANING )
Mom .
( GRUNTING )
Looks like another heart attack
but I can 't confirm it till the autopsy .
Damn .
The waiter says he saw this guy coming out of the John
about five minutes before the body was found .
And who might that have been ?
Frank Bannister .
He was as white as a sheet and shaking .
Waiter thought he 'd been sick .
Damn .
Hi , Lucy . Lucy ?
No .
Dr. Lynskey works for me . We 're colleagues .
Look , Doc , she 's a material witness , all right ?
Okay .
Walt , Bannister was last seen in the restaurant parking lot .
He took off at high speed .
( SIGHS )
Bring him in .
( TIRES SQUEALING )
Hey ! Look at that .
( GROWLS )
( SCREAMING )
( HONKING )
( GROANS )
So your dead husband was having dinner with you at the restaurant ?
What did he order ?
( SNICKERS )
Oh , God . Excuse me .
Timmy .
( INAUDIBLE )
Timmy , front desk , please .
Thank you .
Lucy , this is Special Agent Milton Dammers of the FBI .
I came by train .
I was going to take the flight
but I didn 't feel good about the plane .
At what time precisely
did Bannister leave for the bathroom ?
You . Uh ...
I 'm not sure , precisely .
Did he use excessive amounts of table salt during his meal ?
What ? Answer the question .
For Christ 's sakes , it 's really late .
I can 't remember that , okay ?
( GAGGING )
Oh , God . What is this ? ( RETCHING )
Excuse me , Lucy , I 'll be right back .
Milton ?
Sorry , Sheriff .
I have a problem with women yelling .
Milton , can I get you anything ?
Sheriff Perry !
You are violating my territorial bubble .
Uh-huh .
( EXHALES )
Lucy , you 're still grieving .
It would be very easy for a man like Frank Bannister
to take advantage .
You have such closed minds . I can 't believe it .
I object .
Special Agent Dammers
has over 20 years experience in the area
of paranormal psychology .
Much of that was spent undercover with various
cults and sects .
I get all the fruity cases , Mrs. Lynskey .
For God 's sake , Milton , would you come inside and sit down ?
I 'm more comfortable standing . Thank you .
I really don 't see what this has to do with Frank Bannister .
Mrs. Lynskey , you know nothing about Frank Bannister .
You claim he 's a bona fide psychic
yet all I 've heard is a lot of ill-informed , meandering waffle .
On the third day of July 1990 ,
Frank Bannister , then a successful architect
was overseeing the construction of his new home .
Now , the building contractor , Jacob Platz , would later confirm
that Bannister had been consuming alcohol that morning .
12 : 23 p. m . , Platz sees Bannister
in a heated argument with his wife , Debra .
It appears that Bannister had promised Debra a garden
in the new home
and then , without consulting her , proceeded to lay
a four-inch thick concrete slab
creating a basketball court for himself .
12 : 31 p. m .
Platz watches the couple drive away .
Bannister kept a tool box in the back of his car .
And in it was a utility knife with a retractable blade .
Bannister purchased seven new blades
that morning
at Jesson 's Hardware Store and Building Supply
on the corner of 3rd and Garrett .
( WHISPERING ) 3rd and Garrett .
Third of July .
Seven blades . Three .
Milton , you 're mumbling . We can 't understand a word you 're saying .
12 : 33 p. m .
and their ' 84 Volvo heads into the hills .
It is the last time anyone will see the couple together .
Now , by Bannister 's own admission ,
the argument continues to rage
reaching the climactic point when Debra demands that Bannister stop ,
pull over , let her out .
And at that moment , probably 12 : 36 , 12 : 37 p. m .
the car leaves the road on a sharp curve
presumably because Bannister was driving too fast .
She was killed ?
Her body was found some 15 yards from the car .
Now , Bannister ,
he was picked up two hours later , wandering in the woods .
He claimed to have no recollection of the events that occurred
after the accident .
But here 's the odd thing , Mrs. Lynskey .
His utility knife was missing .
And to this day it has not been found .
But do you know what was really bizarre ?
Debra 's corpse had the number 13
carved into its forehead .
Unlucky for some .
Oh , come on . You 're out of your mind .
You 're talking about a mythical figure .
A pseudo-religious icon from the 12th century .
Save your pea brain prattle for the classroom , boy .
That was the soul collector
and he 's been taking people out since time began .
He 's going about some dark business here in Fairwater
and we ain 't nothing but worm bait .
When your number 's up , ( CLICKS TONGUE ) that 's it .
There 's another one gone .
( INAUDIBLE )
He 's gone .
There 's no money for you here , Mr. Bannister .
You 're next .
Are you threatening me ?
No , that 's not what I 'm saying .
He 's threatening to kill me .
Would you just relax , all right ?
Just listen to me and ...
He 's threatening to kill me .
Bannister ! Oh , great .
Hey , fellows . Okay . Excuse me .
What are you doing ?
Excuse me .
Put the gun away , all right ? Freeze .
All right , everybody , just take it easy .
Whoa , whoa !
Just stay there , Bannister . Stay there .
( GUNSHOTS )
( LAUGHS )
Yes .
( SNARLING )
Ah ! Great .
I did it .
Judge .
Uh-uh , uh-uh . Bannister , stop .
Looks like I ain 't shooting with blanks no more .
( LAUGHING )
Mighty fine woman .
Good teeth .
OFFICER : Now put your hands on the podium .
Judge .
They don 't call me the hanging judge for nothing .
Stay right there .
Heads up .
Good catch .
( PEOPLE SCREAMING )
Freeze !
Whoa ! Good shooting , Tex .
And she was so young and beautiful !
I like it when they lie still like that .
( BOTH GRUNTING )
This is heavy .
( EXCLAIMING )
( GROWLING )
JUDGE : My juices are flowing again .
Judge !
Bannister !
CYRUS : Go , Frank . Just get out of here now .
Bastard !
( GROANS )
Gotta go .
Bannister ! Stop .
( BOTH EXCLAIMING )
( GUNSHOTS )
( ENGINE STARTS )
( ENGINE FALTERS ) Damn . Come on .
( SCREAMING )
( GASPS )
Just get down . Get down and stay down .
MAGDA : Oh , no .
( WAILING )
( INAUDIBLE )
( SOBBING HYSTERICALLY )
Magda ! No ! No !
Listen to me .
( GRUNTS )
( PANTING )
( GROWLING )
Oh , God .
( MAGDA SCREAMING )
No !
( MAGDA CHOKING )
Oh , no .
You killed me , you bastard !
You 're sick . Is this how you get your kicks ?
Did it feel good killing me ?
Bannister , did it feel good killing your wife ?
You 're a murderer !
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( SCREAMING )
I don 't believe he 'll get very far .
We 've got the state line covered .
Sheriff Perry ,
I seriously doubt we will see Mr. Bannister any time soon .
The man is resourceful beyond anything you can comprehend .
Hello , Frank .
Hi , Walt .
I 've come to report that Magda Rees-Jones'
body is lying near my car
off Holloway Road .
Frank , did you have anything to do with her death ?
( EXHALING DEEPLY )
Frank !
Frank , are you okay ? What happened ?
What are you doing ?
Are you arresting him ?
Please leave , Mrs. Lynskey .
Frank . Frank , you need a lawyer .
Go home , Lucy .
But you haven 't done anything . He hasn 't done anything .
How do you know ?
You know me ?
Am I a nice guy , Lucy ? ' Cause
that cozy little scene in the restaurant was bullshit ,
I was doing my job .
And I don 't give a damn about you .
I don 't give a damn about anybody .
What the hell are you saying ?
Go home .
Okay .
Lucy , are you okay to drive ?
Yeah .
Got a kiss for honey bunny ?
I know , I know . It 's the way I look .
It 's this damn ectoplasm stuff .
Turns you off , doesn 't it ?
Come on , Lucy . You 're not listening to me !
Well , look , you know we have a great relationship .
It 's just that lately I don 't feel that you 've been giving it your 100 % .
There has been a destructive force unleashed on this town
such as I have never seen .
We have a body count of
twenty-eight .
You 're a very dangerous man , Mr. Bannister .
For Christ 's sake you 're not seriously suggesting
that Frank is responsible for ...
You 're way out of your depth here , Sheriff Perry .
Please leave .
Frank Bannister is my prisoner .
By the power invested in me by the President of the United States
I am telling you
to get the hell out of this room .
Have you ever heard of Nina Kulagina ?
March 10 , 1970 . Nina Kulagina with the power of her mind
stopped the beat of a frog 's heart .
The record of this experiment is currently held
in the files of Professor Gennady Sergeyev
of Saint Petersburg .
And as Sergeyev interpreted this cardiogram
it seemed to him that the heart had experienced
a sudden flare-up of electrical activity .
The heart imploded , the arteries burst
and all because Nina Kulagina wanted the animal dead .
I don 't kill people .
There 's a part of you that believes that .
There 's another part of you , Frank ,
that 's out of control .
Your destructive impulse .
I 've seen a figure in a cape .
I 've seen him reach into people 's chests and squeeze their hearts .
Who was it ?
Death .
I can communicate with the other side .
I can see spirits .
I don 't know why . I can 't understand it .
You think you 're quite unique , don 't you , Mr. Bannister ?
But in my business , I deal with your type every other week .
This Death figure
is nothing more than a homicidal alter ego
that satisfies your compulsion to kill .
No .
Every time you want to take somebody out
Death figure suddenly appears , does the job for you .
It 's your rational mind 's way of absolving yourself of guilt .
( SCOFFS ) No !
When did you first start seeing spirits , Frank ?
After Debra 's death ?
You killed your wife .
No !
I have studied the coroner 's reports of every death in Fairwater since 1985 .
Twenty-eight cases involved crushed hearts .
Arteries choked until they burst .
That started in 1990 with your
beautiful wife , Debra .
She was the first .
Ray Lynskey .
You have an argument with him , three hours later , dead .
Magda Rees-Jones , we know you didn 't like her .
But what about the guy in the toilet ?
What did he do to you , Frank ?
( FRANK SHUDDERING )
Piss on your Hush Puppies ?
Why are you shaking ?
Oh , my .
You 're doing it right now , aren 't you ?
You 're trying to kill me . Right now .
Forget it , Bannister .
I 'm wearing a lead breastplate !
We have 28 unexplained deaths here .
You know what I think ?
I think you are involved in each and every one of them .
This way .
Mmm .
No .
Hey , man ! Pulling your drawers off . Man , what the hell ?
Benny ? My man , Benny ! Stu , this is my boy here , Benny , man !
Hey , Benny , I 'm your friend , man . Seriously .
Three words , " Shower with soap . "
Come on !
Stu , you all right ?
Spasm , spasm . It 's all right .
Frank . Frank , we got problems .
These cats are gonna stitch you up on a capital offence .
These murders that have been going on in Fairwater ,
they 're gonna pin ' em on you .
Stu and I are gonna get you out of here , so come on , man , let 's go .
STUART : Frank ?
Frank ! Come out of it , man .
Wait , no , wait , wait .
Oh , God . Forget it , Stu .
Look at him .
He doesn 't believe anymore .
It won 't be long now .
He 's reached the acceptance stage .
Grappling with his guilt .
Seeking resolution .
You realize , Agent Dammers ,
we have no forensic evidence linking him with any of the deaths .
Doesn 't matter .
I expect this case to suicide long before it ever reaches trial .
They always do .
So much for the dream home .
What the hell are we doing here , Lucy ?
I mean , look at this place . It 's a dump .
God , this guy 's a loser .
Oh , my God , Lucy .
Look at this . Look at this .
He set us up , Lucy . The man set us up .
This is our house !
He took us for a couple of schmucks , Lucy .
Look , Lucy , look !
( EXCLAIMS )
( PHONE RINGING )
Perfectly good basketball court gone to pot .
FRANK ON ANSWERING MACHINE : Yeah , Bannister .
( PHONE BEEPS )
MRS. BRADLEY : Mr. Bannister , you 've got to help me .
My daughter , Patricia Arm Bradley ,
is communing with the evil one .
He 's in this house at her instigation .
( PATRICIA CRYING ON PHONE )
Help me . Help me drive them out .
( HANGS UP )
( GASPS )
Lucy , I don 't know why you keep shutting me out .
I still have a lot to ... ( EXCLAIMING )
Lucy !
Patricia .
Dr. Lynskey .
Patricia , are you all right ?
( BUCKET RATTLING )
( GASPS )
It 's your mother , isn 't it ?
Your mother 's the one who 's been hurting you .
She needs help . She 's delusional , Patricia .
You can 't go on like this .
You don 't understand .
No !
My father killed himself after the murders .
Mother says it was my fault .
So I have to keep his ashes in my room .
Oh , my God .
She says I 'm evil
just like Johnny .
( SOBBING )
Come with me to Mother 's room .
LUCY : This isn 't you .
This isn 't who you are now .
It was Johnny .
He went crazy .
I couldn 't get away from him .
I thought he was gonna kill me .
Patricia , you have to get out of this house .
You can start over .
( DOOR BANGS ) ( GASPS )
( SHUDDERING FEARFULLY )
It 's Mother . Please hide . Please .
I 'll take her to the kitchen .
You sneak out later .
( GASPS )
What are you doing in my room ?
I thought I heard a noise .
I 'll make you some coffee , Mother .
( DOOR CLOSING )
( CROCKERY RATTLING )
Mother , coffee 's ready .
Lucy , go .
( GASPING FEARFULLY )
Frank .
Thank you , Deputy .
Just call me when you 're done , Dr. Lynskey .
Yes .
Frank . Frank , listen to me . I found your knife .
It was hidden in old lady Bradley 's closet .
She 's crazy , Frank .
You haven 't hurt anybody .
You 're a good person , Frank .
Don 't do this .
( SIGHS ) Please don 't do this .
Jesus , do you think that you 're the only person
who 's ever lost somebody ?
God , you walk around like you don 't have any feelings
but the truth is that you 're just scared .
You 're a goddamn hypocrite . Why are you doing this ?
What are you afraid of , Frank ?
I don 't want to hurt you , Lucy .
Oh , that 's crap . Don 't give me that .
Look at me .
No . Uh-uh . I 'll be outside .
This shit is like walking in on your parents .
Oh , right . Yeah , I 'll just be outside . I 'll just ... Whoa !
What is it , Frank ?
Look out !
You son of a bitch .
( GROANS )
( CHOKING )
( GASPING )
What 's happening ?
CYRUS : Grab him !
( CYRUS AND STUART EXCLAIMING )
Okay . Listen . Listen to me .
Call for the deputy and try to sound calm .
Deputy , I 'm ready to leave now .
Stuart , where did he go ?
I think we got him .
( SCREAMING )
Shit .
No , you son of bitch ! Get out , Frank ! Go !
Frank !
This way . Go .
( YELPS )
Freeze , Bannister !
All right .
Help . I got you now .
Please help me . He 's gone crazy .
All right .
Stay back .
Now ...
( COCKS GUN )
( SCREAMING )
Frank , come on !
Go , Frank ! Get out here ! Please ! Now !
Frank , let 's go !
No , this way . Come on .
Shit !
What was that in that cell , Frank ?
I felt something crushing my heart .
I can 't fight him , Luce . I can 't protect you .
There 's only one way to deal with this thing .
I got to have an out-of-body experience .
What ?
And I got to have it right now .
No !
Go away , Luce . Just walk the other way .
Wait .
This will slow your heart rate and lower your body temperature .
You 'll have 20 minutes , max .
Any longer than that and there 's a danger of tissue damage .
That 's only if I can successfully revive you
and there 's no guarantee .
Frank ,
you don 't have to do this .
Lucy , better close the door .
Hurry up .
It won 't take long .
( GROANS )
( SHIVERING )
( GASPS )
I didn 't know you had an interest in cryogenics , Dr. Lynskey .
I 'm reviving him at 9 : 00 .
Why would we want to do that ?
Luce .
Lucy .
Whoa !
There we go .
( GROANING IN RELIEF )
Let me go , you bastard . Let me go !
Let me out now , you bastard ! Let me out of this car now !
( TURNS RADIO ON )
( LOUD ROCK MUSIC ON RADIO )
I find cemeteries very
restful places , don 't you ?
Turn this car around and take me back .
I intend to , Mrs. Lynskey .
In exactly 11 hours time .
Son of a bitch !
No . No .
I knew Charlie .
Spahn Ranch , 1969 .
First assignment .
I was the family 's sex slave for six months .
Six months
in the service of my country disguised as a whippy shippy .
I want out .
Let me out of here ! Come back here , you creep !
( GASPING FRANTICALLY )
My body is a road map of pain .
1974 .
Children of Lucifer .
Three years undercover , drinking goat 's blood .
1981 , I infiltrated the Cult of the Dead .
I was involved in ritualistic cannibalism ,
in orgiastic dances
reaching painful thresholds of intense , physical eroticism .
I have withstood excruciating pain ,
but I will not be broken .
I have suffered for my country ,
Lucy .
But pain
has its reward .
The power of the mind
is absolute .
( MUTTERING GIBBERISH )
( ENGINE STARTS )
( GASPS )
Frank .
Frank , is that you ?
I 'm doing this ?
I 'm making the car move with the power of my mind ?
Yes !
No .
Wait !
Get back in the goddamn ground
you unorganized grab-asstic gob of teleplasmic shit !
( SCREAMS )
Who in the hell are you ? Sound off like you 've got a pair !
( EXCLAIMS )
FRANK : Hey , asshole .
( GASPING )
( SCREAMS )
( MILTON SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY )
( SNARLS )
Who are you ?
( LAUGHING MENACINGLY )
Johnny Bartlett .
I thought guys like you fried in hell .
I got out , Frank .
I 've been carrying on the good work . Got me a score of 40 .
( LAUGHING )
Harry Sinclair .
I just want to shake the hand of the man
who finally avenged my death .
You 've got a number .
Bartlett carved it into my forehead as I lay dying .
I was the last .
He couldn 't be more wrong , could he , Frank ?
Shit !
( GROANS )
( EXCLAIMING FEARFULLY )
No ! Don 't use it .
No .
( GASPING )
Frank . Okay . Just breathe .
Breathe slowly . Breathe .
Okay . You 're okay .
Okay . Frank .
All right , Lucy , come on .
A hundred milligrams of lidocaine .
Get me one cc of adrenaline , quick , now .
( GROANING )
I didn 't get him .
Who ?
Who didn 't you get , Frank ?
Johnny Bartlett .
He 's back .
He 's hallucinating . It 'll pass .
Lucy ,
he 's killing again .
Patricia .
Lucy , you got to get her out of the house .
Go !
( GASPING )
Patricia ! Patricia !
Listen to me . We have to get out of here .
MRS. BRADLEY : Patricia never leaves the house .
I 'm sorry , Mrs. Bradley , but she 's coming with me .
You have no right . She 's my daughter . Get upstairs .
No . Look , this is gonna stop now .
What are you talking about ?
Why do you have Frank Bannister 's knife in your closet ?
You went in my room ?
Mother .
Patricia .
( RATTLING )
( CLOCK CHIMING )
Mother wants to go to the police now .
No ,
she 'll be down in a few minutes .
No , Patricia , we have to go now .
It 's just not safe here . Johnny Bartlett 's back .
I know .
He visits me at night .
I don 't know why he comes .
He torments me .
Why has he come ?
Am I being punished ?
Patricia , please . Let 's just go now , please .
I wanna kill her now , Patty .
That 'll give us 41 .
That 's eight clear of Gacy .
Another nine and we 'll have broken Bundy 's record .
I can 't wait to see old Ted 's face when he hears the news .
Yes !
What ?
I 'm sorry .
We really should wait for Mother .
And that asswipe psychic nearly ruined it for us tonight , Patty .
He made us look stupid .
You 're gonna be okay , Patricia .
Everything 's going to be all right .
Shut up .
That Russian cannibal creep 's running around
saying he did 50 plus .
That reflects badly on the both of us , Patty .
This record should be held by an American .
I quite agree .
You can come
stay with me if you like .
I 'm going to kill her now , baby .
I 'd like that .
( GIGGLING )
I 'll just get my coat .
Patronizing do-gooder bitch !
Patricia ,
you kill her , I 'll watch .
( EXCLAIMS )
I love it when you do that , baby .
Mrs. Bradley ?
Mrs. Bradley , are you coming with us ?
( GASPS )
Oh , my God .
( SCREAMING )
( SHOTGUN FIRES )
Lucy !
No , not that way !
( SCREAMING )
Jesus , Lucy .
Oh , my God . These are Johnny Bartlett 's ashes .
What ?
We gotta get these to the other side .
For what ?
A church . We got to get them to a church .
There 's a chapel . There 's a chapel in the old hospital .
All right .
No !
No , let 's go down here .
Okay .
Damn it !
( PATRICIA GRUNTING )
Okay . You see that door ? Hold on , let me see .
You look up there . Okay .
( PEOPLE CHATTERING )
Thank you .
Lucy ?
This is great .
Frank ?
Excuse me , Doctor , we 're looking for Ward 12 .
Go up the stairs to the fourth floor
down the corridor to your right .
It 's just opposite the chapel .
NUN : Thank you .
I 'll get someone to help . Orderly .
Orderly , are you deaf ?
I said , Orderly , are you deaf ?
Moron !
I guess that makes you number one .
Get down !
Frank , are you okay ?
The chapel 's on the fourth floor .
( WOMAN SCREAMING )
Frank , watch out !
( GUNSHOT )
( PATRICIA LAUGHING )
Gotta go . Go !
( GROANING )
Lucy .
Lucy !
You 're all the same .
( GROANING )
Wait !
No !
( GASPS )
Put the gun down , son . The law is on its way .
What 's the score , Patty ?
Eleven .
That 's the same as Starkweather 's .
We have a tie on our hands .
( WOMAN SCREAMING )
( GUNSHOT )
Lucy .
Frank .
It 's jammed .
Take it . Just take it . Right .
I 'll be right back . Don 't go anywhere .
No .
( GRUNTS )
Give that to me .
Let me guess .
You have to get these ashes to consecrated ground
in order to destroy the forces of evil .
Give me the goddamn urn , Dammers !
Under no circumstances must these ashes ever be released .
No !
( GROWLING )
Oops .
You have no idea what you 've just done .
You just don 't get it , do you , Frank ?
Your pathological mindset had made it necessary
for you to interpret your sad , personal inadequacies
as a grand struggle between good and evil
in order to gratify your pathetic need for self-glorification .
You are such an asshole .
Yes , I am . I 'm an asshole
with an Uzi .
Get up !
You make me sick ! Get up !
Turn around . I don 't want to shoot you in the back .
Turn around ! I said , turn around !
As an agent of the United States Government
I am ordering you to turn around .
Frank !
Please ! Please don 't hurt me . Stop !
( PATRICIA LAUGHING )
Please !
Frank !
Oh , my God . Frank .
Debra .
You killed her .
( MOANING )
You 're next , pal .
Take him out , baby .
( GUN CLICKS )
( BOTH EXCLAIM IN FRUSTRATION )
No ! Get him !
( FRANK SCREAMING IN PAIN )
No ! Stop !
Frank !
No !
Get him , Patty .
Yeah , baby .
( GASPING )
Whoo ! ( LAUGHS )
Oh , baby , you are an artist .
You 're pretty , too . No !
No .
Yes .
( GRUNTING )
I 'm in the mood for a little vivisection .
( CRYING ) No ! Oh , please .
Me , too .
You bitch !
No !
I got your girlfriend , Johnny !
Come and get her !
No , goddamn you ! Let go of her !
Johnny ! Come and get her , you coward !
Come on and get her !
No !
Let go off my Patty !
Patty !
( PATRICIA SCREAMING )
PATRICIA : Johnny !
Come here . Give me your hand .
( EXCLAIMING )
See you later , Frank . We got you . ( LAUGHS )
We 're going back down to get us some more !
CYRUS : Yo , Frank .
How 's it going ? ( CHUCKLES )
Bye , Frank .
( BOTH EXCLAIMING )
Johnny .
Step back , Frank . Yeah .
This isn 't going to be pleasant .
( BOTH SCREAMING IN ANGUISH )
( EXHALES )
The old express bus to hell . No lines , no waiting .
It 's really something , isn 't it ?
Excellent libraries .
Premium cigars .
And of course , the honeys .
Yeah , how about that ? Stu 's a regular chick magnet up here .
( CHUCKLES )
Hello , Frank .
It 's time to go home .
I am home .
( STUART AND CYRUS EXCLAIMING )
BOTH : No .
STUART : You see , the authorities have informed us
that it 's just not your time .
Start living , dude .
( EXCLAIMING )
Be happy .
( LUCY SOBBING )
Frank !
There 's something I have to tell you .
Yeah ?
( GROANS )
Sorry to interrupt you , folks .
It 's all right , Walt .
Frank , what do you know about Ouija boards ?
Not a lot .
I found a whole stack of them up at the Bradley house .
It looks like Patricia just got herself a direct line
to her dead boyfriend as soon as she was released five years ago .
It seems like the old lady ,
when she caught wind of Patricia 's involvement in ,
well , in your wife 's death , that she just kept the girl sedated .
She just couldn 't stop Bartlett , though .
Nice epilogue , Walt . It was well delivered .
Frank .
Just one other little thing . Uh-huh .
I got a whole bucket load of vacation time coming to me
and I thought ... Good .
... I thought you and I
could collaborate on a book about all this .
It could be my ticket off the force .
That 's not really my area .
If you 're looking for a collaborator
how about your guardian angel over there ?
( LAUGHS )
You got me , Frank .
I got you , Walt .
I 'll see you , Frank . Bye-bye .
Boy , that Dammers , he sure looks pissed .
Yeah .
Well , sometimes , Frank , you see
when you go through a traumatic experience
it kind of alters your perception .
No .
( LUCY LAUGHING )
( BOOING )